[theme music playing]
[laughs]
[Camia] Now isn't the time
to give up. Keep fighting.
[Lily] Take justice into my own hands?
If that's what they want,
then I might just give it to them.
What's your plan now, Boss Jaguar?
The Ardientes have become more powerful
with Red Dragon on their side.
[henchman 2] Shouldn't we be
joining their group now?
Don't you worry. We'll bring them down.
[Arnaldo clapping] Great acting, everyone.
[Helena] One day, I'll pay you back
down to the last cent.
We don't know the exact location
of the damn treasure.
[Arnaldo] The only way to the treasure
is through Grandma's princess.
[Helena] I'm going to make you
the protector of my hidden wealth.
Just guard it with your life.
[Julio] I know the right person
who can spy on your mother.
[Noel] We couldn't get the court
to release a search warrant.
Wasn't the evidence we presented enough?
I am not a vigilante.
It's my job to make sure
the law is enforced.
[Lily] If the law enforcers
can't do anything about it,
then I guess we'll have
to do things my way.
[Diego] Once we get our hands
on Helena's fortune,
we can't surrender it to the authorities.
The Ardientes are in power,
and I'm sure they'd all just get it back.
We'll destroy all of Helena Montoya's
illegal businesses.
[Diego] From now on,
we'll face every single challenge
in our lives together.
[Lily] We'll face everything together.
Just the two of us.
-[Helena] Emilia.
-Yes, Mama?
Survey the area, and make
necessary adjustments
to increase security, okay?
Yes, Mama. I'll make sure that
even the devil himself
won't be able to find
or steal your fortune.
-Very good.
-Bye, Mama.
-[Emilia] Let's go.
-[car engine starts]
[suspenseful music playing]
[ominous music]
Yes, Governor.
Did Emilia just leave the house?
-Yes, Governor. I'll follow her.
-Good.
Now, get me my money.
[chuckles]
[exhales]
[commander] The Madam's here.
Commander.
[commander] Madam Emilia.
Madam Helena said you'd be here.
That's right. I'm here
for the routine inspection.
-So, shall we begin?
-Yes, ma'am.
-Let's go inside.
-Great.
[suspenseful music playing]
[commander] You two, guard the gate.
[goon] Yes, boss.
Ma'am, we're keeping this place
on 24-hour surveillance
with a total of 25 guards on duty.
Okay.
Where's my mother's money pit?
Ma'am, it's a bit further ahead.
Oh, is that so?
Then I will have to ask
my guards to get my shoes
because I can't walk in these heels here.
-[commander] No problem.
-Mike.
-[Mike] Yes?
-Please go get my shoes.
[tense music playing]
[action music playing]
[commander] Madam,
here's the site's control room,
and there's the money pit.
[Emilia] So all of my mother's
wealth is in there?
Yes, Madam.
[sighs]
You know, I know you have
enough men to guard this.
But what if they just send
a rain of bullets your way?
What if someone poisons you all?
What's going to happen, then?
How are you gonna be able
to protect this property
and my mother's money from intruders, huh?
It'll be near impossible for anyone
to even attempt to enter, Madam.
Uh-uh. That's the reason why I'm here.
We'll tighten the security of this place,
and I'll make sure
it'll really be impossible for
any intruders to get in here.
Yes, Madam.
Okay.
Hmm.
Well, you have good facilities here.
My freedom is for the people of Ardiente.
And for my dearest Julio.
-Viva Ardiente!
-[all] Viva Ardiente!
Once again, to our friends in the media,
thank you very much for coming,
and once again, I present
to you, Helena Montoya.
And don't be surprised that soon,
she will be Helena Montoya-Ardiente.
[dramatic music playing]
-Viva Ardiente!
-[all] Viva Ardiente!
[applause]
[suspenseful music playing]
It's good we parked here.
We won't be spotted here.
Things will be tough if we're caught.
-Ready.
-Let's go.
Are you okay back there?
[sensual music playing]
Get dressed.
[suspenseful music playing]
Wait. Wait.
A car's coming.
Bingo. Emilia's car is parked here.
That means Helena
Montoya's wealth is in here.
Colonel. Security's tight.
I can see that. I'm not stupid.
But we have no choice.
[exhales] Security will
really be tight in there
because she's hiding billions in there.
We don't have the time for surveillance.
The governor told us to just strike.
We can't let anyone get their hands
on Helena Montoya's wealth before we do.
So, boys…
[gun loading]
Get ready for battle.
That's Magbanua!
What are Julio's men doing here?
Madam, it looks like we have visitors.
We should get more men.
No need.
It's time to give them my little surprise.
Calm down, friends.
We're with Mrs. Emilia Ardiente.
She's inside, right?
Just wait here, sir.
We'll just verify that with her.
-Okay.
-[grunting]
-[screaming]
Diego, we can't let the Ardientes
take Helena's fortune first. Let's hurry.
[action music playing]
Be on your guard.
[exhales]
Let's go.
[tense music playing]
[gunshots]
How did that happen?
How did Magbanua
enter the place just like that?
And where are the other guards?
It's impossible no one's
guarding the site.
[Julio] Thank you. Thank you.
-[Helena] Thank you very much.
-[Julio] Thank you.
-Thank you very much for coming.
-Thank you.
[Julio] Thank you. Thank you.
Thank you to all of you.
Thank you for taking time today.
Thank you. Thank you to everyone.
Go ahead. A couple more pictures. Yes.
[camera shutters clicking]
There you go.
[whispers] Helena, if you like
being called my first lady,
maybe you should also learn to play along
and pretend that you love me.
[whispers] Why don't you dream on, Julio?
You know that I don't love you.
I want you to be my partner.
You deal with the politics,
while I run the syndicate.
We will be the most powerful
couple in the land.
You know what, Helena?
No matter what you say,
I still love you so much.
Even if I know you're hiding
something from me.
I know you've got
this hidden wealth somewhere.
And word on the street is
that you've got billions
tucked away in a secret place.
Just be thankful that I'm only
asking for half of that.
[giggles]
-Go straight ahead.
-Yes, sir!
-[explosion]
-[men scream]
[groans]
[laughing]
Emilia, good job.
-[Lily] Are you okay?
-[Diego] I'm fine.
Let's stay here for now
until the situation dies down.
-[Helena] Well…
-Thank you very much. You can go now.
-Thank you. Thank you.
-Please go over there.
Thank you.
-Thank you.
-Keep dreaming, Julio.
Dream on.
And catch me and my money if you can.
Helena.
I always charge with interest.
It might be too much for you.
[fire blazing]
[groans]
[commander] Madam Emilia.
You have to leave.
Of course, I am leaving, Commander.
Because I can't wait to hear
my father's voice
once I tell him that I've caught
him and his stupid men.
But first…
[phone rings]
Magbanua?
Emilia?
Governor. A landmine blew up at the site.
Hello, Mama. Papa's men
and Col. Magbanua are here.
-They tried to raid us.
-What?!
[ominous music]
[tutting]
Sir… We didn't get the money.
[dramatic music playing]
[exhales]
You bastard!
That was very rude of you.
It's a good thing
the press were gone already.
[dramatic music playing]
[goon] Hurry! Get rid of the bodies!
[panting]
Are you okay?
Over there. Let's head there. Come on.
[suspenseful music playing]
The pain will go away eventually.
Someday, I'll be able to look
Jepoy in the eyes and tell him,
"Thank you for your love and betrayal.
Because of that, I became stronger."
But I need time.
You know, one day, you'll meet
someone who'll love you right.
Just look around you.
Don't be silly.
Marlon and I are just friends.
-[chuckles]
-[Arnaldo] Okay.
I guess Arnaldo
isn't just a pastor,
he could be a love guru.
[Arnaldo laughs] You're right.
Actually, if you asked me,
I'd rather live here.
'Cause the more time
I spend with my family,
the more I feel that I'm different.
[Marlon] So that's why you weren't there
when Helena Montoya
met up with the Ardientes.
Yeah. I mean, think about it.
She managed to escape all the
complaints filed against her.
So, I'm sure Lily would feel hurt
if she saw me supporting my family.
You said it.
Anyway, I better get going.
The teachers are waiting for me.
All right. Take care.
-By the way, where's Lily?
-Oh, Lily's with Diego.
You know those two.
They don't like losing.
They don't like losing? What do you mean?
They said they would take down
all of Red Dragon's businesses.
They'll try to look
for her hidden wealth too.
You don't say.
Excuse me, I'll just follow Anna.
Sure.
[Marlon] Anna.
[ominous music swells]
[suspenseful music playing]
[heavy breathing]
[panting]
[suspenseful music playing]
I want to help Lily in her mission.
But first, I'll ask my former colleagues
where Red Dragon's secret armory is.
-But what if--
-Camia, please.
I need to do this.
[Helena] Yes, I am a dragon.
But you, Julio, you're an anaconda,
acting all nice, calling me first lady.
Meanwhile, you were coiling around me,
so you could strangle and eat me up.
It's because I can't trust you.
You really thought you could
outsmart someone like me?
You know why I helped you
get out of prison?
Because I thought
we were going to be allies.
No! You offered me freedom
because you thought you could
fool me long enough to steal my fortune.
Only to find out that
once your tactics failed,
you tell your lackey to do it for you.
That's so low. Even for you, Julio!
Hey, I didn't do it! Magbanua acted alone!
Yeah right, Papa!
Colonel Magbanua wouldn't act
without your orders.
And I was there, remember?
I set the landmine.
Your men fell into my trap.
You fell into my trap.
Shut up, you freeloader!
Stop riding on your mother's coattails!
Everybody, stop, okay?
Grandma, you shouldn't
be angry with Grandpa.
Yes, he wants to be compensated.
But the one who really wants
to steal your wealth
and your remaining businesses
is none other than…
[imitates drum sound]
Lily Cruz!
-No.
-Yes.
Lily Cruz can't do that. No!
[whispers] Lily Cruz again?
[dramatic music playing]
This is it.
That's where Red Dragon hides her fortune.
We can do this, Lily.
[action music playing]
-[mahjong tiles rattle]
-[woman] Hi, sir!
Just enjoy, okay?
Looks like we're going to win.
[man 1] Money, sir? Have a drink.
[woman] Sir, good evening. How many…
[man 2] One.
[woman] Here. Here. This way.
[suspenseful music playing]
[guard] Sir, do you have an invitation?
Sir? Sir?
[grunting]
[action music playing]
[man 1] Go.
[tense music playing]
[man 2] Hurry. Hurry.
[man 1] That'll do.
We'll just go eat.
You guard while we're gone.
-All right.
-Let's go.
[Ed] Hey, bro. I'll just go on patrol.
[man 2] Sure.
Welcome, sir.
[Jepoy] Get out of here.
-[guard] What was that, sir?
-I said, get out of here!
Why is that, sir?
[grunts]
[people clamoring]
[Jepoy groaning]
[action music playing]
[Ed] Hey! Who are you?
[grunts, groans]
[man] Ed?
[grunting]
[Jepoy groans, grunts]
[groans]
[grunts]
[man] Ed, where are you? Are you okay?
Ed?
-[Damian grunts]
-[man grunts, groans]
[groaning]
[grunting]
-[gunshot]
-[women screaming]
[tense music playing]
[screaming]
[Jepoy] Everybody out.
[screaming continues]
-[Jepoy] Go on, get out of here.
-[women] Thank you, sir!
[Jepoy] Go back home to your families.
[suspenseful music swelling]
-Get out!
-[woman screams]
[action music playing]
[grunts]
[suspenseful music playing]
[lighter clicks open]
-[glass shattering]
-[fire blazing]
[fire blazing]
[Helena] Well, I better go.
I have to warn the armory,
the site, and the brothel.
I'm going with you.
[Helena's phone rings]
What?
[suspenseful music swelling]
This can't be happening!
-What's going on?
-It's Lily Cruz!
She's destroying everything!
I'm going to destroy her!
She can't do this to me.
I'm gonna destroy that witch
with my fangs!
No.
If she was able to destroy
your brothel and the armory,
the next thing
she'll destroy is your wealth!
[Emilia] Oh my God!
-[Helena] No!
-Let's go!
[Helena screaming]
The money!
[Emilia sighs]
Okay, I guess I'm coming.
[phone vibrating]
[quietly] Jepoy?
Jepoy's burned down the brothel.
Very good.
[tense music playing]
[loud explosion]
[phone vibrating]
[quietly] Uncle Damian…
[Damian] Lily…
Tell Jepoy not to go
to the armory anymore.
I burned it down.
I'm ready to help you out, Lily.
Thank you. Thank you, Uncle.
All right.
[man] Help! Help! Help! Help me!
Help! Help! [coughs] Help!
-Somebody, help me! [coughing]
-Stop yelling! I'll help you!
[man] Help me!
[ominous music]
Uncle Damian's burned down the armory.
Let's finish this.
Let's go.
You ready?
I'll go first.
[suspenseful music playing]
Intruders!
-[grunts]
-[groans]
[man] Riz! Riz, get down here!
We need backup! We're under attack!
[gunshots]
[gunshot]
[man groans]
[men groaning]
Men, let's go!
[gunfire]
[grunting]
[screams]
[groans]
[groaning]
[action music playing]
Diego.
[Lily] The keys…
Get the keys.
[action music playing]
[Diego] Let's go.
[chain clanking]
[gate opens slowly]
Wait. Stop.
Hang on.
We can't just walk in there.
One wrong step,
and it might be the end of us.
-[electric spark]
-Hold on.
It might be easier this way.
[panting]
[tense music playing]
[electric spark]
[action music playing]
[Diego] Follow me.
-Be careful, Diego.
-All right.
[Diego groans]
Lower your head.
[suspenseful music playing]
[Diego] Raise your foot.
[electric spark]
-[Lily groans]
-Be careful.
[Diego] Slowly.
This one's harder.
[Lily] A bit more.
[suspenseful music playing]
[electric spark]
[Diego grunts]
[upbeat music playing]
[Lily exhales]
[Diego] Your turn. Okay.
Diego.
[Diego panting]
[Lily] Wait.
Step back then lower your body.
That's right.
Step back.
[Diego] There you go.
Be careful.
You can do it. You're almost there.
[tense music playing]
I'll go down first.
[suspenseful music swelling]
Hey, make it fast!
Do I always have to tell you?
Julio…
Lily Cruz can't get that money.
That money is my whole life!
When you left me,
I devoted all my time to the syndicate.
All the time
I should've spent raising Emilia
went to making that fortune.
If I lose it all, I'll have nothing left.
Everything will be lost! Everything!
[dramatic music playing]
[Diego groans]
[electric spark]
[Lily] Just leave it.
-[Diego] These are enough.
-[Lily] Yeah. Let's go.
[Lily yelps]
[alarm blaring]
[Lily] Let's go. Hurry.
[both groan]
[Lily] Hurry up!
[alarm continues blaring]
If we only had more time,
we could've taken
all of Red Dragon's money!
Lily, these are enough.
Let's go!
[alarm continues blaring]
Hold on, Lily.
[tense music playing]
[alarm continues blaring]
-[loud explosion]
-[Helena screams]
[Helena] No! No!
[suspenseful music playing]
[Helena] No!
No!
[cries]
My money!
-[Emilia] Mama!
-My fortune!
[Emilia] Wait! No!
[wailing]
-Mama!
-No!
[Helena wailing]
[Emilia] Mama.
-[Helena wailing]
-[somber music playing]
[fire crackling]
[somber music playing]
[Lily] Hurry!
[suspenseful music swelling]
[upbeat music playing]
Let's go.
[fire blazing]
[somber music playing]
[suspenseful music]
[Julio] I'm mad because I was outwitted.
You bastard! I trusted you!
-And this is how you repay me?!
-[Jepoy groans]
Huh?!
This might convince you to talk.
[screams]
Does it hurt?! Talk!
Hang him upside down!
Now!
[somber music playing]
[Anna sobbing]
Nanny, I couldn't protect you.
[Arnaldo] I can kill you
and make it look like
you committed suicide,
just like what I did to Carlotta.
[Natalie] I missed you, Madrigal.
-Hmm?
-[giggles]
Jepoy?
[Anna crying] I was so stupid to think
you'd be different from other men!
But it turns out you're worse!
In case you've forgotten,
you were mine first.
[Natalie yelps]
[grunting]
[Natalie screams]
[Lily] I've done everything I can.
I put Arnaldo in prison…
And Emilia too.
I took Julio's power from him.
And I've put Red Dragon
behind bars, but what happened?!
Our plans all end up in smoke!
Too many people have sacrificed,
so much for this!
Including their lives!
But for what? After I have them locked up,
they'll walk out scot-free
after a few days.
[dramatic music playing]
To all the monsters in this world!
I hope you all burn in hell!
[loud explosion]
[dramatic music playing]
[engine revving]
[upbeat music playing]
[slow instrumental playing]
Mister, can I have some change?
Spare change, mister.
Miss, spare some change, please.
I'm really hungry. Mister,
can I please have some change?
Hey, this is real money!
Wow! Oh, there's another one!
This is a lot!
It's raining money! Wow!
[woman 1] That's a lot of money!
A lot of money!
[woman 2] Money!
[unintelligible]
[cheering]
We've clipped your wings, Red Dragon.
Now you'll crash right into hell.
Happy landing.
Did you see their smiles?
That's because of you.
You mean the two of us.
We both did this.
And we did the right thing.
We only gave back what
the Ardientes stole from them.
As long as we're together,
nothing will ever stand in our way, Diego.
We will rebuild Poblacion Ardiente.
[romantic music playing]
I think someone's tailing us.
[suspenseful music playing]
Step on it!
[man] They can't get away!
[suspenseful music playing]
[Magbanua] You have to see this.
That happened in the next town.
Someone made it rain money.
My money! My money!
[screams]
-Do you have a plan?
-I do.
We need to drive them out of this town.
That way, we can ensure peace and safety
in Poblacion Ardiente.
I will help you crush Lily Cruz.
[Emilia] I love my family.
[Arnaldo] Are you and Lily
going somewhere?
[Diego] Somewhere special.
[Arnaldo] By special, do you mean
you'll propose to her?
[theme music playing]